you.
I'm trying to find that boy I knew In shades of
brilliant white and blue The one I thought he had
it made Before the colors start to fade He's
still in here, a distant ghost The one I miss and
fear the most A part of me is lost, it's true A
space that was reserved for you
But the scars remain a map to trace And they found
their proper place I'm standing on a different
floor Than I was standing on before And I can hear
a brand new sound This new and solid ground The
echo of a worried flute A sound that stands as
loving roots
I'm learning how to trust again To let the gentle
sunlight in I'm learning that a helping hand Can
help a broken boy to stand I'm learning that a
home can be A fortress built for only me By two
strong women, brave and true Who know exactly
what to do Does the scars remain? I'm out to trace
and there I found the proper place I'm standing
on a different floor than I was standing on
before and I can hear a brand new sound ♪ On this
new and solid ground ♪ ♪ The echo of a worried
flute ♪ ♪ A sick disease with loving roots ♪ ♪ Did
you feel it? ♪
Hey.
you